Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) photographs, audiovisual, and publications, 1944-2014 MS2374
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audio/Visual material, Series 2
  - Downtown Progress, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 5)
  - Fare Collection Spot (2)/ Fare Collection Equipment, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 6)
  - Go #4, 1976; Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 7)
  - Go #6, 1978; Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 8)
  - Go #9, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 9)
  - Go #10, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 10)
  - Metro Here and Now, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 11)
  - Metro Here and Now #14, Series 2 (Box 64A, Folder 12)
  - Metro Here and Now #51, Series 2 (Box 64B, Folder 1)
  - Metro Here and Now #62, Series 2 (Box 64B, Folder 2)
  - Metro Here and Now #81, Series 2 (Box 64B, Folder 3)
  - The Coming Way Tp Go, 1977; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #1, Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 1)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #3, Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 2)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #4, Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 3)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #8, 1975; Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 4)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #9, 1980; Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 5)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #10, Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 6)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #11, 1982; Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 7)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #20, Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 8)
  - A-2 Earth Tunnels #21, 1982; Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 9)
  - Concept into Design/ Cubic - Film on AFC, Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 10)
  - Downtown Progress "Metro"/ 3 TV Spots, Series 2 (Box 107C, Folder 11)
  - Fare Collection Equipment/ Fare Collection Spot, Series 2 (Box 107D, Folder 1)
  - Go #5, Series 2 (Box 107D, Folder 2)
  - Go with Metro Color, Series 2 (Box 107D, Folder 3)
  - Le Metro: "Best Trip in Town", Series 2 (Box 107D, Folder 4)
  - Metro Bus/ Metro Film Bank, Series 2 (Box 107D, Folder 5)
  - Metro Here and Now, Series 2 (Box 107D, Folder 6)
  - Metro Progress Filmport/ Wheelchair at Dulles Airport, Series 2 (Box 107D, Folder 7)
  - Misc WMATA Film Reels, Series 2 (Box 107E)